A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Chancellor of the Virginia Community College System, 1964-2012
Library of Virginia
- Series IV: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 43865], 1970-2003 [bulk 1995-2001]., Extent: 13 cu. ft. (13 boxes). (Box 1-13)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Tidewater Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Wytheville Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Signature Authority, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Longwood University, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Dept. of Human Resource Management, 2002 (Box 10)
  - VCCS Presidents, 2002 (Box 10)
  - CFAC, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Controller, VCCS, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Council of Presidents, 2002 (Box 10)
  - U.S. Dept. of Education, 2002 (Box 10)
  - U.S. House of Representatives, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, Chancellor, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Chancellor's Cabinet, 2002 (Box 10)
  - State council of Higher Education (SCHEV), 2002 (Box 10)
  - Office of the Governor, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Comptroller, State of Virginia, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Secretary of Education, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Fiscal Services, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Dept. of the Treasury, 2002 (Box 10)
  - U.S. Dept. of Justice, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Secretary of Transportation, Virginia, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Vice PResidents of Administrative and Financial Services, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Community Colleges Association, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Workforce Council, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Dept. of Social Services, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Academic Services, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Workforce Development Services, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Human Resources, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Facilities Management Services, 2002 (Box 10)
  - JSRCC Trip, 2001 (Box 10)
  - GCC Trip, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Video and audio cassettes (Box 11)
  - A World Class Workforce: The Virginia Community College System's Second Defining Moment, 1998 (Box 12)
  - Non-Credit Funding: Chancellor's Briefing to HJR 622 Joint Study Committee, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Creating and Sustaining an Information Technology Future in The Virginia Community College System, 1994 (Box 12)
  - How Virginia's Community Colleges Contribute to Virginia's Economic Future, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Outcomes of the VCCS Professional Development Initiative: 1993-1998 (Box 12)
  - College and Campus Development of the Virginia Community College System, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Focus for the 1990's: Virginia Community College System Planning Document, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - Model of Child Care on the Community College Campus, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Directions Task Force Recommendations, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Final Report: HJR No. 143 Study of Preparing a Skilled Workforce, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Directory of Distance Education and Telecommunications Options, 1993 (Box 12)
  - The VCCS Library Automation Task Force's Transitional Report, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Northern Virginia Community College: An Oral History, 1965-1985 (Box 12)
  - Virginia Community College System- Review of the Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission Staff Report, 1975 (Box 12)
  - Toward the Year 2000: The Future of the Virginia Community College System (Box 12)
  - Report of the Chancellor and the Virginia Community College System, House Document No. 10, 1993 (Box 12)
  - Virginia Community College System Strategic Plan, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Distance Learning Action Plan, 2000-2003 (Box 12)
  - Workforce Development Initiatives, Report for Fiscal Year 1999 (Box 12)
  - Restructuring Plan Virginia Community College System, Executive Summary, 1994 (Box 12)
  - VCCS-Wide Courseware Project Final Report, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Report of the Committee on Dual Enrollment Fees, HJR 562, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Task Force: Strategies for Attracting, Selecting and Retaining Faculty, 2002 (Box 12)
  - VCCS Technology Plan 2000 (Box 12)
  - VCCS Organizational Strategy for Distance Learning, Final Report, 2001 (Box 12)
  - VCCS Professional Development, Report by the VCCS Professional Development Task Force, 1993 (Box 12)
  - Professional Development Initiative, 1994 (Box 12)
  - The VCCS Professional Development Initiative, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Vision 2000: Meeting the Needs of Learning Communities, 1994 (Box 12)
  - VCCS Distance Learning Management Model Implementation Committee, Final Report, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
  - VCCS Voice over IP Project Report, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Broadening the Base of Higher Education in Virginia, Dissertation, 1970 (Box 12)
  - VCCS Enhancing Support for Adjunct Faculty (Box 12)
  - VCCS Principles of Good Practice for Dual-Credit Programs (Box 12)
  - Completing Their Dreams- An Alliance for Virginia Students, 2003 (Box 13)
  - College Board Member Handbook, ca. 2001 (Box 13)
  - VCCS Photo Directory, 1989-1990 (Box 13)
  - VCCS Photo Directory, 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - Directions, Transfer Information Directory, ca. 1989 (Box 13)
  - Classified Staff Professional Development Committee Meeting, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Assessment of Development - Income Potential for Property at Tidewater Community College, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Community College Assessment Reports, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Non-Credit Funding, Chancellor's Briefing to HJR 622 Joint Study Committee, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Nomination for SCHEV Outstanding Faculty Award for Virginia Nichols Quinn, 1996 (Box 13)
  - The VCCS Professional Development Initiative, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Restructuring at New River Community College, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Substantive Change in Distance Learning Activities at New River Community College, 1995 (Box 13)
  - VCCS Draft Strategic Plan 2000-2002 and 2002-2004 Biennium, 1999 (Box 13)
  - VCCS Program Guide, 1994-1996 (Box 13)
  - VCCS Annual report, 1989-1990 (Box 13)
  - Final Report: HJR No. 143 Study of Preparing a Skilled Workforce, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Toward the Year 2020, The Future of the VCCS (Box 13)
  - Blue Ribbon Strike Force, Final Report to the Governor, 1994 (Box 13)
  - JLARC, Program Evaluation of the VCCS, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Refocusing Higher Education in Virginia, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Science and Technology, HJR 195, 1996 (Box 13)
- Series V: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 44420], 1964-1997 [bulk 1983-1997]., Extent: 8 cu. ft. (8 boxes). (Box 1-8)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Rappahannock Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Tidewater Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Western Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Wytheville Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, Finance, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Wytheville Community College, Building and Development, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Western Community College, Building and Development, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Tidewater Community College, Building and Development, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, Building and Development, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, Building and Development, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Rappahannock Community College,Building and Development, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, Building and Development, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, Building and Development, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Wytheville Community College, Educational Foundation, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Western Community College, Curriculum and Programs, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, Curriculum and Programs, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, Curriculum and Programs, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Wytheville Community College, Curriculum and Programs, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, Curriculum and Programs, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Western Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Tidewater Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Rappahannock Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Wytheville Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, Audit, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Western Community College, President's Office, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, President's Office, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Tidewater Community College, President's Office, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Tidewater Community College, Presidential selection, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, President's Office, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, President's Office, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, President's Office, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Rappahannock Community College, President's Office, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, President's Office, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, President's Office, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, President's Office, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, College Board, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Tidewater Community College, College Board, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, College Board, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, College Board, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Rappahannock Community College, College Board, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, College Board, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, College Board, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, College Board, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, Misc., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Southwest Community College, President's Office, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Attorney General, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Attorney General, General Law Review, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Studies and reports, ca. 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - The Effect of a Reduction in Tuition on Enrollment Fall, Volume II, Appendices, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Outcomes of the VCCS Professional Development Initiative, 1993-1998 (Box 2)
  - Virginia Community College System Master Plan (1982-1990), 1983 (Box 2)
  - Toward the Year 2000, The Future of the Virginia Community College System Long Range Plan, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Pursuing the American Dream, A History of the Development of the Virginia Community College System, 1987 (Box 2)
  - The "Ins and Outs" of Marketing and Retention in Virginia's Community Colleges, Volume II, 1987 (Box 2)
  - Background Papers, Volumes I and II, ca. 1988 (Box 2)
  - Legislative Proposals, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Executive Vice Chancellor Correspondence, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Salary Freeze, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Educational Telecommunications, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Emergency Services, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Faculty and Classified Staff Structure, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Education, Dept. of, U.S., 1992 (Box 3)
  - Fiscal Services, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Focus for the 90's, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Executive Council, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Meeting, School to Work Act, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Finance, Secretary of, 1993 (Box 3)
  - VCCS Foundations at the Colleges, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Virginians for Progress, Bond Reference Steering Committee, 1993 (Box 3)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 3)
  - U.S. Congress, Virginia Delegation, 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - Board meeting, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Grievance procedure training, 1995 (Box 4)
  - President's memorandum, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Information Technology, Dept. of, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Old Dominion University, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Penn State University, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Motorola, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Library Automation Committee Taskforce, 1995 (Box 4)
  - James Madison University, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Information Technology Services, Vice Chancellor, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1995 (Box 4)
  - FIPSE meeting, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Financial Aid, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Functional Inventory, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Education, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 4)
  - General Assembly, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Comptroller, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Attorney General, Office, of, 1964-1996 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Space Grant Consortium, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Visually Handicapped, Dept. of, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1996 (Box 5)
  - V-Quest, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Code Commission, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Economic Bridge Initiative, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Technology Governance Task Force, 1996 (Box 5)
  - State Police, Dept. of, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Veterans Affairs, Dept. of, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - SCHEV (State Council of Higher Education), 1996 (Box 5)
  - Workforce Services Job Training proposal, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Workforce Leadership Council, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Waste Management, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Wheat First Securities, Inc., 1992 (Box 6)
  - Vocational Education, Virginia Council on, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Volunteerism, Office, of, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Staff correspondence for the system office, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services, Vice Chancellor, 1996 (Box 6)
  - Review of student fees, 1994 (Box 6)
  - SCHEV meetings, 1997 (Box 6)
  - GPAC (General Professional Advisory Committee), 1997 (Box 6)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Plato, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Southern Association of Community, Junior, and Technical Colleges, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Sabbatical leave, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Richmond Public Schools, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Statistical data, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Community College Planning: A Common-Sense Approach, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Ten Years of Higher Education in Virginia, 1987 (Box 6)
  - VEDMARS (Virginia Employer Data Management and Reporting System), 1987 (Box 6)
  - Workforce Training and Service Needs of Virginia businesses, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Virginia Sales and Tax Expenditure Study, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Opportunity Virginia Steering Committee, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Virginia Space Grant Consortium, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Governor's Employment of Training Dept., 1990 (Box 7)
  - Governor's Job Training Coordinating Council, 1986-1989 (Box 7)
  - Professional Development Initiative Bellwether Award, 1997-1999 (Box 7)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, 1988-1994 (Box 7)
  - Budget Allocation Model, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Congress, 1993 (Box 7)
  - California State University, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Capital Construction Initiatives, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Catonsville Community College, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co. Proposal, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Chancellor, Misc., 1993 (Box 7)
  - Christopher Newport College, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Chief Business Officers, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Clinch Valley College, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Citizen Ambassador Program, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Commencement dates, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Commonwealth, Secretary of, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Chancellor's conference calls, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - Enrollment adjustment, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - Employment and Training, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Health Professions, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Infrastructure Task force, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Illinois Community College, 1993-1994 (Box 7)
  - VCCS Conference on Reading, 1993 (Box 7)
  - School to Work Transition Programs, SJR No. 183, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Cooperative agreement with State Board of Vocational Education, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Continental Health Promotion, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Committee to Promote Higher Education, 1993 (Box 7)
  - General information, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. 1994 (Box 7)
  - Acclaim Regional Advisory Board, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence received, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Congress, U.S., 1994 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence to presidents, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Governor, Office of the, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Correctional Education, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, General, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, General, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Education, Dept. of, 1983 (Box 7)
  - VCCS Presidents "Planning and Evaluating for Fundraising Success,", 1994 (Box 8)
  - VCCS Presidents memorandum, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Hiring freeze, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Education, U.S. Dept. of, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Education, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Contracting Authority, 1993-1994 (Box 8)
  - Capital outlay, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Recruitment for Instructional Technology Initiative Team, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Governor, Office of the, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Agriculture and Consumer Services, Dept. of, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Administration, Secretary of, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Commerce, Dept. of, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Commission on the University of the 21st Century, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Commission for the Arts, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Artist in residency, 1990 (Box 8)
  - College mission, VCCS, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Colonial Storeage Company, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Colleague Consultants, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Clinch Valley College, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Cheshire County Council (England), 1990 (Box 8)
  - Capital Outlay, Bureau of, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Central Health, Inc., 1990 (Box 8)
  - Central Virginia Industries, Inc., 1990 (Box 8)
  - Calhoun Community College, 1990 (Box 8)
  - CASE (Council for Advancement and Support of Education), 1990 (Box 8)
  - Congress, Virginia Delegation, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Comptroller, Office of the, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Community College Review, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Gallaudet University, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Early Childhood and Child Day Care Programs, Commission on, 1990 (Box 8)
  - House of Delegates, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Defense, Assistant Secretary of, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of, 1990 (Box 8)
  - FTES, 1990 (Box 8)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Wytheville Community College, Building and Development, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, Building and Development, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Tidewater Community College, Building and Development, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, Building and Development, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, Building and Development, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Rappahannock Community College, Building and Development, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, Building and Development, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Wytheville Community College, Educational Foundation, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Tidewater Community College, Educational Foundation, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, Educational Foundation, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, Educational Foundation, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Tidewater Community College, Curriculum and Programs, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, Curriculum and Programs, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Wytheville Community College, Curriculum and Programs, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, Curriculum and Programs, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Rappahannock Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, Enrollment and Admissions, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, Accreditation, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, Misc., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, Misc., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Rappahannock Community College, Misc., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, Misc., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Southwest VirginiaCommunity College, Misc., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, Misc., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Tidewater Community College, Misc., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Wytheville Community College, Misc., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Western Community College, Misc., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, Misc., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Wytheville Community College, President's Office, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Tidewater Community College, President's Office, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, President's Office, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, President's Office, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, President's Office, 1991 (Box 8)
- Series VI: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 45267], 1969-2008 [bulk 1995-2004]., Extent: 15 cu. ft. (15 boxes). (Box 1-15)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Danville Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Danville Advanced Technology Center, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Germanna Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - John Tyler Community College, Midlothian campus, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - New River Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, Medical Education Campus, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, Regional partnership, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Tidewater Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Highland Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Wytheville Community College, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Danville Community College, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Germanna Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - John Tyler Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Lord Faifax Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - New River Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Piedmont Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Tidewater Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Wytheville Community College, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 2000 (Box 3)